ISRAA MAZARAA

Ramallah

https://www.linkedin.com/in/israa-mousa-691950211/

github.com/Israa-Mousa/0592385684

israa.mazaraa@yahoo.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Talented QA with two years' experience and two years expertise In Develop Coding using PHP and ASP.NET MVC. Successfully monitors and controls all phases of Constuction and testing using Jira. Works collaboratively within multi-functional teams to identify and resolve bugs and functionality issues. Strong technical analysis and quality assurance skills.

EXPERIENCE

PUBLIC INSITUTION, RAMALLAH

SOFTWARE ENGNIEER, part time

10/2022 - present

- -Build a new application using special template for the institution on Grails platform.
- -Customized existing system for new needs.
- -Testing the system for new requirements.
- -Finds bugs and solve them

GAMIPHY, RAMALLAH

QUALITY ASSURANCE ENGINEER, part time

10/2022 - 04/2023

- Working with JIRA system.
- Testing of application.
- -Report the bugs and writing test cases.

FOOTHIL, RAMALLAH

QUALITY ASSURANCE INTER

11/2022 - 02/2023

- Learn more about the testing process.
- Write testing cases with template.
- -Start with automation Quality Assurance.

HADARA, RAMALLAH

FULL STACK ENGINEER

07/2021 - 04/2022

- Work with BAGISTO e-commerce system on Laravel framework.
- Customize the project for new requirements.
- Use Laravel framework, with CSS, HTML, JS, bootstrap and PHP languages.

ASAL, RAWABI

Quality Assurance

09/2020 - 06/2021

- Work with Microsoft Dynamic 365, add new features with the CRM and make flow for some tasks.
- Make tests plan for the new spec and write their test case and try to find the bugs and report them to the developers.

GO-GLOBAL, RAMALLAH

Quality Assurance Internship

11/2019 - 01/2020

- Train with Go Global company as quality assurance.
- Learn about QA principles and how to write test plan using Azure Devops

EDUCATION

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN COMPUTER ENGINEERING, BIRZEIT UNIVERSITY

06/2014-06/2019

Computer system engineer-minor of business administration

SKILLS

- Manual testing
- Reports bugs using Jira
- Cypress skill: writing test cases, Cucumber Testing and typescript.
- Debugging
- CSS, bootstrap , JS &HTML.
- PHP and Laravel framework
- Python for data science.
- Asp.net

- Mobile testing.
- API testing using Swager
- Writing test cases using test trail tool
- Cypress skill: writing test cases, Cucumber Testing.
- JavaScript and Type script.
- Grail's platform
- SQL.

LANGUAGE

- Arabic.
- English.

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

CENTER OF CONTINUING EDUCATION BIRZIET

DATA SCIENCE TRAINING 12/2021-4/2022

- Learn basics of python.
- Data frame on python.
- Full explority data analysis report-

GAZA SKY GEEKS

LARAVEL TRAINING 12/2021-2/2022

- Learn the basics of PHP.
- Learn Laravel framework.
- Make full application project.

REFERENCES

• Maram Duibes: Gamiphy company-0569393007

• Amr Rajab: Hadara Company-0597221376

• Rasha Bazbaz: Asal company-0598499971

Note:

-You can see my Certificate on the link https://github.com/Israa-Mousa/Resume

-You can see my projects on my linked in account